♪ I'll try to be a cat ♪ (According to the Literature Reading Group author monster monster if the fire novel work "today also want to be a cat" adaptation)
=Kucingku, Pacarku=
[Episode 23]
= Episode 23 =
Please pay attention to it.
Mohon perhatian semuanya.
The new work of Si Chen and I
Karya baruku dengan Kak Si Chen
We will have more works in the future.
Ke depannya kita akan memiliki lebih banyak karya lagi.
Stay tuned.
Semuanya mohon ditunggu.
I've done everything you asked.
Aku sudah melakukan semua yang kamu minta.
When will you release him?
Kapan kamu melepaskannya?
We just announced our relationship.
Kami baru saja mengumumkan hubungan cinta.
What's your hurry?
Kenapa kamu terburu-buru?
Killing Pei Zhen will not benefit me.
Membunuh Pei Zhen juga tidak ada untungnya bagiku.
What else do you want to do?
Apa lagi yang ingin kamu lakukan?
Don't worry.
Tenang saja.
I don't care about you
Sekarang aku
Has no interest at all.
Sudah tidak tertarik sama sekali.
However
Tetapi
I'm still interested in the resources
Aku masih sangat tertarik
More interested.
Lebih tertarik
It's so sweet.
Manis sekali.
Give me a kiss.
Cium satu, cium satu.
Pei Pei.
Pei.
You said you liked me back then.
Bukankah dulu kamu bilang suka padaku?
What's the situation now?
Bagaimana keadaannya sekarang?
Now I like you.
Sekarang aku menyukaimu.
You threw me off again.
Kamu mencampakkanku lagi
Are you feeling accomplished?
Apakah kamu melakukan ini sangat memuaskan?
You scum.
Dasar pria berengsek.
Say something.
Bicaralah.
I'll listen to your explanation.
Aku dengar penjelasanmu.
I can listen to your explanation.
Aku bisa mendengarkan penjelasanmu.
This is my cat, Jerry.
Ini kucingku, Jerry.
Cute, right?
Imut kan?
I want to...
Aku ingin...
When I went out today,
Pasti saat aku keluar hari ini
I forgot to feed it cat food.
Lupa memberinya makan kucing.
So it came out to chase me.
Dia baru bisa keluar mengejarku
Pei Pei.
Pei.
Jerry, Master Cat.
Kepala Jerry Puss,
Shoveling shit officer is wrong.
Petugas buang kotoran salah.
After I went back,
Setelah pulang,
I'll give you cat sticks as compensation.
Sebagai gantinya,
Pei Pei's world collapsed.
(Dunia Pei runtuh)
I had a telepathic connection with her.
♪ Dan aku melakukan telepati dengannya ♪
I can understand her.
(Bisa mengerti apa yang dia katakan)
Pei Pei.
Pei.
Are you all right?
Kamu baik-baik saja?
Don't take it too hard.
Kamu jangan berpikiran pendek
Commander Fu.
Fu Si Chen.
Pei Pei.
Pei.
Don't scare me.
Kamu jangan menakutiku.
Don't do anything stupid.
Kamu jangan melakukan hal bodoh.
To do something stupid.
Melakukan hal bodoh.
You think too much about Nian Nian.
Kamu berpikir terlalu banyak, Nian
I won't do it for others' mistakes.
Aku tidak akan demi kesalahan orang lain
To punish myself.
Untuk menghukum diriku sendiri.
I just want to be human again.
Sekarang aku hanya ingin menjadi orang kembali.
And take care of them.
Lalu bereskan mereka berdua.
Wait
Tunggu sebentar.
My door is closed.
Pintu sudah kututup.
You can't go there.
Kamu tidak boleh ke sana.
to close
Tutup pintunya.
Why did you close it?
Kenapa ditutup?
I'm still lying inside.
Tubuhku masih berbaring di dalam.
Xiao Nian
Xiao Nian.
You'd better tell me the truth.
Lebih baik kamu jujur padaku.
No animals were harmed during the filming.
(Tidak ada hewan yang terluka saat syuting film ini)
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.) (Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)
(Hak siar jaringan informasi serial kembali) [Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.] Eksklusif untuk menikmati)